

1

+974 3997 6325



yahyasabiri61@gmail.com



Qatar



www.yahyasabiri.com

SKILLS

- Physical endurance
- Creativity
- Leadership
- Kitchen Safety
- Team Collaboration
- Attention to Detail
- Time Efficiency
- Negotiating the prices of food and necessary ingredients

LANGUAGES

English - conversational Arabic - Native French - Beginner

HOBBIES

Body-Building Parkour

Yahya **Sabiri**

CHEF

A professional chef with six years of experience in Moroccan and Qatari cuisine and experienced in managing kitchens that serve about 70 tables. I have the ability to motivate employees and ensure that kitchen operations are done with great focus and results. I have the ability to create modern dishes using fresh seasonal products, and meet a wide range of dietary restrictions.

EDUCATION

PASTRY AND BAKERY ARTS

Amal center 2017 - 2018

EXPERIENCE

CHEF SUSHI

Miss Mix Shop - Nawar's Bakery Aug 2022 - present

• sushi, pasta, corndog, mozzarella

CHEF

Yamine hotel

2020 - 2021

• pizza ,sandwich, burger, pasta, tacos

PASTRY AND BAKERY SPECIALIST

Dilicia bakery

Mar 2019 - Apr 2020

Brownies, Palmiers, various types of cake, baguettes,
The salty (mini pizzas, mini tacos, small and regular-sized burgers) and different kinds of Mille-feuille

COOK AND SERVICES

Ouzoud hotel

Dec 2018 - Mar 2019

• salads, Moroccan tajines, crepes, and pasta